Greatness demands sacrifice.
HIM is a horror, mystery film directed by Justin Tipping.
After suffering a potentially career-ending brain trauma, Cameron Cade receives a lifeline when his hero, legendary eight-time Championship quarterback
and cultural megastar Isaiah White, offers to train Cam at Isaiah's isolated compound that he shares with his celebrity influencer wife.
But as Cam's training accelerates, Isaiah's charisma
begins to curdle into something darker.
Isaiah, played by Marlon Wayans.
Cam, played by Tyriq Withers.
Elsie, played by Julia Fox.
Tom, played by Tim Heidecker.
Marco, played by Jim Jefferies.
Malek / Horned Fanatic, played by Maurice Greene.
Him is a 2025 American supernatural horror film
co-written and directed by Justin Tipping.
The film stars Marlon Wayans, Tyriq Withers, Julia
Fox, Tim Heidecker, and Jim Jefferies.
Its plot follows a young up-and-coming football player (Withers) training at the
isolated compound of an aging, nearly retired quarterback (Wayans).
Him was released in the United States on September
19, 2025, by Universal Pictures.
It received generally negative reviews from critics and grossed
$28 million against a budget of $27 million.
The film explores themes of ritual, cult, training, religion, injury.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.